{
    "subject": "resource/Charlie_Chaplin",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:English_film_score_composers",
    "human_readable": "Charlie Chaplin is about English film score composers.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9878486394882202,
            "question": "Is Charlie Chaplin associated with English film score composers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8208460211753845,
            "question": "Who are some famous English film score composers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4964770972728729,
            "question": "How did Charlie Chaplin influence filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4961157441139221,
            "question": "What type of artist was Charlie Chaplin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4738389551639557,
            "question": "What is Charlie Chaplin known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4304288923740387,
            "question": "What is a film score?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3995135724544525,
            "question": "What are some notable works by Charlie Chaplin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3615879714488983,
            "question": "What are some common elements found in English film scores?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2121150642633438,
            "question": "What country is Charlie Chaplin from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18382422626018524,
            "question": "What era was Charlie Chaplin most active in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Charlie Chaplin is about English film score composers.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5817_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Charlie Chaplin from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5817_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common elements found in English film scores?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5817_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some notable works by Charlie Chaplin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5817_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5817_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5817_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5817_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5817_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5817_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5817_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5817_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5817_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5817_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5817_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide various details that support the statement \"Charlie Chaplin was an English film score composer.\" The information covers his transition from silent films to talkies, his ability to conduct and compose music for his films like \"Modern Times,\" and his recognition as a composer in addition to his roles as actor, director, and writer."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The text states Chaplin was a British comedian, actor, director, and composer who made music for his films. There's no indication he focused solely on English film scores.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}